Music
I'm about to start recording.
I'm going to talk with Mr. Yakan.
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
Have you seen other people's videos?
I've seen so many.
They all speak so well.
I'm a little nervous about whether I'll be able to speak as well.
I don't get a chance to talk about myself very often.
I think I was able to show many new eyes.
It was fun.
Is there a third Alasry?
Yes, there is.
The third Alasry is amazing.
And the fourth?
I love solving riddles.
There's the Tokyo Viterrari Circus in Shinjuku.
I go there to solve riddles.
I also like to watch shows about solving riddles.
I also like to buy Zaku and Hope.
I also like to play online real escape games.
I love those kinds of quests.
I just barely didn't get in.
But I love it.
And the third one, Alasry?
This one.
Right now.
What's this?
It's a gumbo.
It's the first gacha gacha
It's the first Gacha Gacha.
I tried so hard.
Only one kind didn't come out.
The one I wanted the most didn't come out.
The original one and the general one, only the panel one didn't come out.
I couldn't get the original one and the general one, only the panel one.
It was so bad!
And the third one, Alasry?
Yes.
It's not so much that it's really kinky.
I think I prefer shoujo manga where the characters are holding something together.
That way, each character is explored in depth.
That's how they came to have this kind of romantic feelings.
I like to read that kind of thing.
I like shoujo manga that properly depicts each person's past and so on.
I think that's totally fine.
People say "shounen manga" and "shojo manga".
I think that if you read a lot of both
I think there are more common stories.
And they're more interesting than anything else.
It's fun to read.
Alasry's booth
Have you been to this booth before, Ms. Hanane?
I don't think we've met here before.
How do you like it?
I wonder why...
Is it part of Yamato Japan?
The owner thinks he's sitting in a booth that's bigger than this one.
He thinks he just sat down.
I'm chewing the air.
It's a big space.
I'm sure I'll be nervous.
But I'm more excited than nervous at the moment.
I'm sure I'll be able to handle it.
What kind of preparation have you done since you decided to do it?
I bought a notebook after the decision was made.
First of all, I'm very anxious.
I've been worried about everything.
Even when I get another job.
I'm always thinking about the next job.
I'm trying to prepare for it.
I decided to buy a notebook and a pen to prepare for it.
So I bought a notebook and a pen.
Then I started to write things down.
I always tend to take notes on my phone.
I moved the notes on my phone over here.
I've been transferring memorable programs I've listened to
I've been transferring my memorable programs to this notebook.
Wow, what should I do?
I wonder why I usually
I usually make a lot of mistakes that I don't know why I make mistakes here.
Like not being able to open the lid of a drink at all
or spilling everything...
I'd like to collect such inconvenience episodes from everyone!
And then share them.
Let me know if you'd like to share your stories.
I'd like to do a corner like that.
I see... I wonder...
That's exactly what Waka-chan from Iinari Toho Kita is doing.
She's a junior who's always said she's my favorite.
So I'd like to talk a lot with her.
I'd like to talk a lot with Wakabayashi and listen to what he has to say about the group.
I love to ask for advice.
I'd like to have a dialogue with him about various things.
The time is 1:30 a.m.
Good evening, this is Haruname.
I'm Haruname, broadcasting live from Studio 2 of the Nippon Hoso Broadcasting System in Yurakucho, Tokyo.
I'm Haru-Name and I'm broadcasting live from Studio 2 of Nippon Hoso Broadcasting System, Yurakucho, Tokyo.
I have a lot of recommendations for you.
I have a lot to recommend.
As a manga artist, I can't choose just one.
A new one has come to my house? I can't get enough of that.
I highly recommend it.
I guess that's what I'm talking about.
My favorite actor
There's an actor named Aoi.
And there's a girl named Sumire-chan who's into young actors.
This is a story about the two of them.
One day, she suddenly came to Sumire-chan's house.
They call him "Kakun".
An actor comes to her house.
came to her house.
What's that?
Is it really so dreamy?
Yes, it is.
What I like best about this manga is...
It's a girls' manga.
But it's more comical than squeamish.
I don't know if you like shounen manga or not.
Even if you like boys' manga or have never read shoujo manga before, it's easy to read.
Really? Is it easier for me to get into it?
It's easy to get into.
Some parts are very touching.
But there are also places that make you feel a certain way.
It's a manga with a great balance between the two.
You guessed it?
My guess came to my house.
I could list many more.
Can I give you more?
I'll say it for the first time, this is love.
I'm going to say it for the first time, is this love?
It's a girl's manga.
It's very heavy.
The main character, Lisa, is an honor student.
She is an honor student in her class.
She's an honor student in her class.
and a mischievous boy named Zen
Zen-kun.
one day, when Zen-kun is in trouble
One day, when Zen-kun was in trouble
when he was in trouble.
Zen-kun tried to repay Lisa-chan's kindness.
From there, things started to happen.
The naughty boy returns the favor.
You can see the serious side of the naughty boy
And you can also see how Lisa, who is an honor student
And you can also see how she's gradually being influenced by Zen-kun.
and the way each of them changes is carefully depicted.
I see.Oh, yeah.
It's really good.
No, I don't feel like a pussy.
You don't do pussy, Zen.
No, Zen, I don't.
You don't?
You're not naughty like that?
I'm not naughty like that.
Yes, you are.
Really? I wonder how naughty he is.
That's not what I meant.
That's not what I mean.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm not trying to lead you down a bad path.
I'm a decent person. I'm a decent person.
I'm a decent person.
I'm talking about the two of you.
This is, uh...
I'm talking about love, in the deepest sense of the word.